Inventory of the Allen Weinstein papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Writings by Allen Weinstein
  - Proposals to publishers regarding The Haunted Wood, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 109: 13)
  - Articles, 1978-2000 (Box-folder 109: 14)
  - Book award, 1979 (Box-folder 109: 15)
- Research materials, correspondence, and drafts
  - Clippings, 1978-2000 (Box-folder 110: 1-3)
  - Serial issues, 1970-1998 (Box-folder 110: 4-7)
  - Miscellaneous documents, 1935-1945 (Box-folder 110: 8)
  - Sobell, Morton, 1957 (Box-folder 110: 9)
  - Rosenberg, Julius and Ethel
    - 1952 (Box-folder 110: 10-11)
    - 1953 (Box-folder 111: 1-6)
    - 1950 (Box-folder 111: 7-8)
    - 1950-1951 (Box-folder 112: 1)
    - 1951 (Box-folder 112: 2-8)
    - 1951 (Box-folder 113: 1-6)
    - 1952 (Box-folder 113: 7-8)
  - Sobell, Morton, 1950 (Box-folder 114: 1-2)
  - Morros, Boris, 1946-1949 (Box-folder 114: 3)
  - "Dvoinoi agent," typescript, undated (Box-folder 114: 4-5)
- Writings by Allen Weinstein
  - Articles, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 114: 6)
  - Papers, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 114: 7)
  - Letter to the editor, 1976 (Box-folder 114: 8)
  - Press release, 1976 (Box-folder 114: 9)
  - Reviews of Perjury and other articles about Allen Weinstein, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 114: 10)
- Research materials, correspondence, and drafts
  - Rosenberg, Julius and Ethel, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 115: 1-5)
  - House Committee on Un-American Activities, 1948 (Box-folder 115: 6)
  - Hiss, Alger, 1934-1948 (Box-folder 115: 7)
  - Daily Worker, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 115: 8)
  - Hiss, Alger, 1933-1975 (Box-folder 116: 1-4)
  - Typewriter (Hiss case), 1948-1974 (Box-folder 116: 5-7)
  - Trilling, Lionel, 1948-1975 (Box-folder 116: 8)
  - Vassana, Nicholas, 1949 (Box-folder 116: 9)
  - Wadleigh, Julian, 1949-1975 (Box-folder 116: 10)
  - Amerasia, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 116: 11)
  - Werschen, Raymond, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 116: 12)
  - Weyl, Nathaniel, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 116: 13)
  - Wyzanski, Charles, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 116: 14)
  - White, Harry Dexter, 1948-1976 (Box-folder 117: 1)
  - Peters, Joszef (pseudonym, Alexander Stevens), 1948-1975 (Box-folder 117: 2)
  - Solow, Herbert, 1933-1961 (Box-folder 117: 3-4)
  - Chambers, Whittaker, 1949 (Box-folder 117: 5-6)
  - Hiss, Alger, 1948-1970 (Box-folder 117: 7-8)
  - Swope, Herbert Bayard, 1950 (Box-folder 118: 1)
  - Sullivan, William, 1975 (Box-folder 118: 2)
  - Welles, Samuel, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 118: 3)
  - Witt, Nathan, 1949-1957 (Box-folder 118: 4)
  - Zabladowsky, David, 1952-1975 (Box-folder 118: 5)
  - Soule, Edmund, 1974 (Box-folder 118: 6)
  - Stripling, Robert E., 1948-1975 (Box-folder 118: 7-8)
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 118: 9-11)
  - Soviet purge trials, 1940-1971 (Box-folder 118: 12)
  - Rosenberg, Julius and Ethel, 1951 (Box-folder 118: 13-14)
  - Typewriter (Hiss case), 1949-1970 (Box-folder 119: 1-7)
  - Typewriter (Hiss case), 1948-1966 (Box-folder 120: 1-6)
  - Hiss, Alger, 1942-1959 (Box-folder 120: 7)
  - Perlo, Katherine Wills, 1949 (Box-folder 120: 8)
  - Massing, Hede, and Lawrence Duggan, 1949 (Box-folder 120: 9)
  - Mehren, Robert B. von, 1948-1976 (Box-folder 120: 10)
  - Morris, Robert, 1958 (Box-folder 120: 11)
  - Murray, Edith, 1950 (Box-folder 120: 12)
- CLOSED (Boxes 121-148)
- Incremental materials (Boxes 149-172)
  Not yet described.